m2epro.com 2016-05-08

# M2E Pro standard website privacy policy. Use of cookies and Google analytics explained. - M2ePro

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We collect information about your company when you submit the form in order to obtain an m2e pro license(s). All correspondence, including but not limited to the technical support, is recorded as well. When you use any of our services, our systems will automatically process your data and may track some information. By using our services you are giving us permission to process, track and store relevant data in accordance with our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions.

WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?

We use the collected information to communicate with you, fulfill your requests, customize the content, improve our services, protect our and your rights, and comply with laws and regulations. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information and updates regarding our services. The information that we collect from you may be used in aggregate form in various ways to optimize and improve our services. While such information may be based on information about you, it will not identify you personally. We may use such information for the following purposes: website management, administration and security, promotional activities, and research and analysis.

HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

DO WE USE COOKIES?

We would like to advise you of the cookies which will be used while you browse our website(s). If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit [Aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance.

DO WE USE GOOGLE ANALYTICS?

We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website, however we do not collect or store your personal information in this respect (e.g. your name, email or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.

DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

THIRD PARTY LINKS

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

CHILDRENS ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

TERMS AND CONDITIONS

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](https://m2epro.com/terms-and-conditions) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website or our services.

YOUR CONSENT

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

FURTHER INFORMATION

Please contact us at support[at]m2epro.com if you require further information or have any question related to our Privacy Policy.
